<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Password123</string>
    <string name="hint">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="network_warning">Low Network - Offline Check Only</string>
    <string name="powered_by">powered by haveibeenpwned.com</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="password_manager">If that all seems like too much effort, I don\'t blame you.
        The best solution is probably to invest in a password manager (I suspect it\'s what most
        security professionals do). Click this card to search for one.</string>
    <string name="about_tech">When you enter a password into Password123, the first thing the app does is
        to convert your password into a one-way hash (a one-way hash is random looking text which is
        difficult to reverse back to the original password - hence "one-way"). Your password is
        still visible to you on the front page though, so be careful that no one is looking over
        your shoulder!\n\n
        From that point on, the rest of the password checking system is only told about your password
        hash, not your full password.\n\n
        The first check that Password123 does is to look in a list of the 10,000 most common exposed
        password hashes. This list is stored in the app itself, so it\'s very quick to check and you
        can still use this feature even when you have no internet connection on your phone.\n\n
        It goes without saying that any password found in that list is extremely insecure and should
        be changed immediately.\n\n
        If Password123 was not able to find your password hash in that list, then so far so good!\n\n Next
        it will try to access the internet to check the main haveibeenpwned.com database (that\'s not
        a typo, hackers like to use the letter p instead of o, go figure). \n\n
        haveibeenpwned.com is not run by a hacker by the way, it is run by Troy Hunt who is a very well
        known security professional who works for Microsoft and tours the globe speaking
        about internet security. The site is continuously updated and exists so that people can
        check if their personal data has been breached somewhere on the internet. I recommend you
        take a look at the site, it\'s illuminating to say the least.\n\n
        The haveibeenpwned.com database has hashed passwords from about 5 billion(!) accounts that
        have been exposed by hackers in the past. You really don\'t want to have a password which is
        the same as one on that list. But if you do, the app will let you know immediately so that
        you can change it.\n\n
        So that not even the ihavebeenpwned.com service knows what password hash you are checking,
        the Password123 app uses the k-anonymity API. Basically this means that only the
        first few characters of
        your password hash ever leave your phone, the haveibeenpwned service replies with all the
        possible matches in it\'s password hash database (usually a few hundred or so).\n\n
        The Password123 app is the
        only part of the system that knows the full password hash, and it checks for a match among the
        few hundred results returned to it from the haveibeenpwned service itself. \n\n The
        haveibeenpwned service
        never knows which of those hundreds of results returned, matched your password - if indeed any
        of them did.</string>
    <string name="licences">Password123 is an open source Android app written in Kotlin, the source is
        available here: https://github.com/erdo/password123 \n\n The app makes use of these third party
        libraries and services:
        \n\n haveibeenpwned \n see: https://haveibeenpwned.com/API/v2#PwnedPasswords
        \n\n OkHttp \n see: https://github.com/square/okhttp
        \n\n pwned4android \n see: https://github.com/erdo/pwned4android
        \n\n ASAF \n see: https://github.com/erdo/asaf-project
        \n\n icons \n see: https://material.io/icons/
    </string>

</resources>
